life is about living it to the fullest
at different stages of your life you
have different goals for you and your
family however in an increasingly
uncertain world you also need to ensure
that your family is financially secured
at all times presenting ICICI pro Luxur
lifelong income of one of its kind plan
which helps you achieve financial
independence with regular tax-free
income till the age of 99 years and
return of premiums on maturity it also
provides life covered till 99 years of
age which helps you leave a legacy in
case of any unfortunate event let us
understand this plan in detail meet mr.
Cooley a 40 year old government employee
he invests in ICICI Prue luck she'll
lifelong income and phase one lakh
rupees every year for 10 years
let's look at the benefits that mr.
Kohli gets regular additions of 10,000
rupees is added to the policy every year
mr. Kohli receives a lump sum of 1.5
lakh rupees in the 15th year
and starts getting regular income of
1.15 lakh rupees every year thereafter
that's not all mr. Kohli will also get
rewarded with tax benefits on premiums
paid and the benefits he gets so delight
your customers with ICICI prove luck
she'll lifelong income
[Music]